# ADAEZE **NDUPU**

Lagos, Nigeria · +2348132284088

Email: andupu4@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/adaeze-ndupu-

Portfolio: <a href="https://vermilion-resume.netlify.app/">https://vermilion-resume.netlify.app/</a>

Adaeze Ndupu is a budding frontend developer with 2+ years of experience converting still-life designs to interactive and responsive websites.

She is a problem solver and pursues user satisfaction from creating websites and products that provide solutions to companies or individuals.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## NOVEMBER 2022 – PRESENT FRONT END LEAD, WAREHÖUZIT

- Developing and implementing user-friendly, responsive web interfaces using React, SCSS, Tailwind and Next.js.
- Collaborating with other developers, designers, and stakeholders to create visually appealing and functional websites.
- Conducting code reviews and quality assurance testing to ensure the website is free of errors, bugs, and inconsistencies.
- Conducting research on emerging web development trends, tools, and technologies to enhance the website's functionality and usability.
- Creating and maintaining style guides and design systems to ensure consistent branding and design elements throughout the website.

#### **JUNE 2022 – DECEMBER 2022**

## FRONT END FELLOW, TIIDELAB

- Carried out User research with a team of developers for a project (Q&A platform) which helped define the users and their pain points.
- Designed User Interface using Figma, implemented with HTML, CSS, Javascript and converted to React.
- Worked in an agile environment with daily stand-ups, material sharing and consumption, and bi-weekly sprint planning and presentation.

#### **JUNE 2021**

## FRONT END DEVELOPER INTERN, SIDE HUSTLE

- Determined structure and design of web pages.
- Replicated pixel perfect and responsive designs while ensuring optimization.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement designs.
- Mentored team members on concepts they faced difficulty with.

Projects: <a href="https://bondee.netlify.app/">https://vermilion4.github.io/dark-theme-landing-page/</a>

# **EDUCATION**

OCTOBER 2021

# HTML, CSS, AND JAVASCRIPT FOR WEB DEVELOPERS, JOHN HOPKINS

UNIVERSITY(COURSERA) - CERTIFICATION

Achieved 100% grade and covered HTML, Javascript, CSS, Responsive design and CSS Frameworks Project: <a href="https://bondee-bistro.netlify.app/">https://bondee-bistro.netlify.app/</a>

**SEPTEMBER 2016 – JUNE 2020 BSC COMPUTER SCIENCE, BABCOCK UNIVERSITY** 

4.4 CGPA on a 5.0 scale.

## **SKILLS**

- HTML
- Next.jsWordPress
  - Git
- Javascript

- CSS
- Tailwind
  UI/UX
  Bootstrap
- React

Webflow